pansypanda.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Pansy Panda

Pansy Panda(s) provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at pansypanda.com (collectively the “Site”).

  1. **Changes.**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy. The changes shall take effect after we notify you about the changes.

  1. **Your Consent.**

By using the Site, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US.

  1. **Information Collection.**

When you contact us or make a purchase through the Site, you provide information about yourself. Depending on how you use the Site, such information that you provide to us includes: (a) your name, email, address, age (to comply with legal requirements), password, alias, and other registration information; (b) your interactions with the Site; (c) communication to us about the Site; (d) information you provide to us when you contact us for help; and (e) any additional information you choose to provide to us.

In addition, we collect certain information, which cannot be used to personally identify any user, and which may be provided to third parties. Such non-personal data ordinarily includes aggregate, summary, or other usage data, and may include, by way of example, statistics regarding total users, information regarding types of Internet browsers used by users, technical information about the device you use to access the Site, and Site usage patterns.

When you make a purchase through the Site, you will enter your payment information through a third-party payment provider. To do so you must agree to that third-party providers terms of use and privacy policy. While we endeavor to use secure payment processing providers, we cannot make any guarantee about the security of such third-party payment provider. We reserve the right to change payment providers at any time.

When you make a purchase from the Site, your content will be delivered to you from a third-party content delivery provider. To accept such content delivery, you must agree to that third-party providers terms of use and privacy policy. While we endeavor to use secure content delivery providers, we cannot make any guarantee about the security of such third-party content delivery provider. We reserve the right to change content delivery providers at any time.

  1. **Use of Information.**

We track usage data and user traffic patterns throughout our Site to improve the content of our Site and the quality of our Site. We may use your information (a) to deliver the Site and features desired by you, (b) to improve our services to you, (c) to personalize content and offers that may be of interest to you, (d) to respond to your inquiries, and (e) to fulfill your request for products or services. We may disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to organizations approved by Pansy Panda that conduct research and to advertisers we allow to advertise on the Site. In no event will such information identify you personally unless you have given your prior consent.

If we have it, we will use your contact information to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information or required notices. We will refrain from sending you emails if you request. If you do not wish to receive emails from us, please respond to an email you receive or email us at [pansypandasite@gmail.com]. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so.

  1. **Cookies.**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We may use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our websites, and their website access preferences. Pansy Panda visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Site, with the drawback that certain features of the Site may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

  1. **Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on the Site are delivered to users by our advertisers. We may from time-to-time use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on the Site.  Advertisers use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies on your browser to help present offers, better target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements by using data gathered on an anonymous basis over time and across their network of Web pages to determine the preference of their audiences. These cookies and web beacons do not collect any personal information from your computer, such as your e-mail address. The use of cookies and web beacons by advertisers is subject to their own privacy policies.

  1. **Children.**

Any user providing personal data is certifying that he/she is over the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use our site. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [ **pansypandasite@gmail.com** ]. We will delete such information from our files.

  1. **Acquisition.**

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of the Site and its products, such as an acquisition by or merger with a company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.

  1. **Security.**

Pansy Pandais very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We may require password protection and use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. We limit access to personal information about you to employees and authorized parties who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information in our possession and control, no security system can prevent against all potential security breaches, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal data or non-personal data arising in connection with the theft thereof. Likewise, you are responsible for safeguarding the confidentiality of passwords to the Site, and we bear no liability for access to, or use or disclosure of personal data if such access, use or disclosure arises in connection with the theft or disclosure (whether intentional or negligent) of such user’s password.

  1. **How to Contact Us.**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, or if you believe there are inaccuracies in your account information you may contact us as follows:

pansypandasite@gmail.com

Last Updated: February 2014
